RG 015, Office of Policy and Management
Connecticut State Library
- Series 14. Management and Justice Planning Division, 1979-1987; 1989-069; 16 cubic feet
  - Subject Files
    - A Diagnostic Report, 1984 (Box 8)
    - OPM Budget and Financial Management, 1983-1987 (Box 8)
    - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
    - FY88 Budget Analysis, 1987 (Box 8)
    - OPM Budget Fees - Outside Professional Services, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Reporting Requirements for State Owned Leased Vehicles, 1986 (Box 8)
    - OPM Contingency Planning, 1986 (Box 8)
    - OPM Comprehensive Planning Div., 1986-1987 (Box 8)
    - OPM NIS Evaluations, 1986 (Box 8)
    - OPM Bank Match Program, 1982-1983 (Box 8)
    - Cooperative Education program, 1986 (Box 8)
    - OPM Copier Task Force, 1984-1985 (Box 8)
    - Data Processing Policy, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Data Processing Committee, 1987 (Box 8)
    - DP Task Force, 1984-1985 (Box 8)
    - OPM - DP Task Force, 1982-1985 (Box 8)
    - OPM Proposed F.A.C., 1985 (Box 8)
    - OPM Data Processing Training, 1984 (Box 8)
    - OPM Data Processing, Word Processing, Wang, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Long Range DP Plan, 1985-1986 (Box 8)
    - Long Range DP Plan, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Long Range DP Plan, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
    - OPM DP & WP Requirements, 1980-1984 (Box 8)
    - DSR Legalized Gambling Study, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
    - DSR-RFP Socio/Economic Impact Study, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Sec. of State - Organization Review, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Office of Sec. of State, 1978-1986 (Box 9)
    - Sec. of State Study Group, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Sec. of State - Board of Accountancy, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Structure of State Government, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 1980-1987 (Box 9)
    - Transportation (Box 9)
    - State Treasurer, Office of, 1981-1986 (Box 9)
    - State Treasurer, Office of (Box 9)
    - Treasurer's Office - Cash Flow, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Treasurer - Procedures Manual, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Treasurer - Management Study, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Treasurer - Unclaimed Property, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Governor's Committee to Review Vet's Home & Hospital, 1987 (Box 9)
    - VH&H Medicaid Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 9)
    - VH&H, 1986 (Box 9)
    - VH&H Management Study, 1986 (Box 9)
    - VH&H Governor's Commission, 1987 (Box 9)
    - VH&H Study, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
    - VH&H Medicaid Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 9)
    - VH&H Review of Overtime, 1984 (Box 9)
    - VH&H Nursing Department Review, 1985 (Box 9)
    - VH&H Proposed Nursing Home, Rocky Hill, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
    - Rocky Hill Vet Home, 1986 (Box 9)
    - OPM Single Agency Audit, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Future of Uncas-On-Thames Hospital (2), 1986 (Box 10)
    - Future of Uncas-On-Thames Hospital, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Uncas-On-Thames, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Uncas Uses (Agency Responses), 1985-1986 (Box 10)
    - OPM Office of Information and Technology, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Request for Proposal Procedures, 1987 (Box 10)
    - OPM Set Aside Program, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Statewide Facility and Capital Plan (OPM), 1981-1986 (Box 10)
    - Supervisor's Guide to Employee, 1980-1984 (Box 10)
    - OPM Tax Reform Team, 1986 (Box 10)
    - RFP - Transportation Accountability Board, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Worker's Comp. Forms (Box 10)
    - Department of Public Safety (Box 10)
    - DPUC Div. of Consumer Counsel, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Public Safety - State Police S.P.R.A.M.I.S., 1984 (Box 10)
    - Public Safety, Office of Civil Preparedness, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Public Safety, Office of State Fire Marshall, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Public Safety, Fire Marshal's Office, State Building Inspection Program, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Department of Revenue Services (Box 10)
    - Department of Revenue Services, Sales of Motor Vehicles, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Casual Sales and DMV (Box 10)
    - DRS, Div. of Special Revenue, 1981-1985 (Box 10)
    - Commission on Special Revenue, 1979-1985 (Box 10)
    - Commission on Special Revenue, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Revenue Services - Management Study, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Special Revenue - Dog Testing, 1985 (Box 10)
    - DIM Feasibility Study, 1987 (Box 11)
    - DIM Rate Setting for Care Facilities (Box 11)
    - Office of Inspector General, 1985 (Box 11)
    - State Insurance Purchasing Board, Self Insurance for State Cars, 1980-1982 (Box 11)
    - Department of Labor, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Department of Labor, Deputy Commissioner Position, 1987 (Box 11)
    - OPM JPTA (Job Training Partnership Act), 1984 (Box 11)
    - Job Training Partnership Act, 1982-1984 (Box 11)
    - Department of Labor - S.O.I.C.C., 1985 (Box 11)
    - Legislative Program and Review Committee, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Department of Education, State Library, 1987 (Box 11)
    - CVH, Employee Day Care Center, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Department of Mental Health, 1985 (Box 11)
    - DMH, DHR, OPM, Homeless Task Force, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Department of Mental Retardation, 1980-1985 (Box 11)
    - DMR, DMH, COR, DCYS, OPM, CADAC Study on effects of Deinstitutionalization, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
    - Training Program for DMR Aides, 1980-1983 (Box 11)
    - CT Public/Private Feasibility Study, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Training Program (Aide), 1980-1981 (Box 11)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles, 1985 (Box 11)
    - DMV - Reorganization, 1986 (Box 11)
    - DMV RFP Review, 1986 (Box 11)
    - MVD-RFP Automated Systems, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Agency Assistance Resource Center, 1981-1983 (Box 11)
    - Directory of Available Services Management Conference, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Evaluation Formula for Proposals, 1984 (Box 11)
    - M&E Evaluation of RFP's, 1984 (Box 11)
    - OPM Flex Time (A&R Contract), 1981 (Box 11)
    - OPM, M&E Impact of Affirmative Action Regulations on State Agencies, 1986 (Box 11)
    - OPM, M&E Bi-weekly Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 11)
    - OPM M&E Monthly Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
    - DP Monthly Reports on Current and Pending Projects, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
    - Leasing Vehicles, Equipment (Box 11)
    - Department of Children and Youth Services (Box 12)
    - Office of the State Comptroller, 1981-1983 (Box 12)
    - Comptroller Accu Tel, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Comptroller FMIS Accounting/Reporting System Project, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Manual for telecommunications (Box 12)
    - Telephone Equipment and Services, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
    - Comptroller Unemployment Comp., 1981-1984 (Box 12)
    - Department of Corrections (Box 12)
    - CT Correctional Industries Advisory Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 12)
    - Department of Correction - Prison Industries, 1981-1983 (Box 12)
    - Prison Industries (Box 12)
    - DOC Inmate Transportation, 1986 (Box 12)
    - DOC Privatization in the Dept. of Correction, 1986 (Box 12)
    - DAS/DOC Evaluation of Contracted Food Service at State Facilities, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Food SVC Project, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Department of Correction Overtime Study, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Dept. of Correction, Review of Financial Clerk, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Department of Economic Development, 1987 (Box 12)
    - State Department of Education, 1983-1985 (Box 12)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1980 (Box 12)
    - State Ethics Commission (Box 12)
    - Office of Fiscal Analysis (Box 12)
    - Office of the Governor (Box 12)
    - Depart. of Agriculture, Governor's "Care & Share" Program, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Department of Health (Box 12)
    - Medical Examiner's Office, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Board of Higher Education, Regional Community Colleges, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Department of Housing (Box 12)
    - Milano Meeting - Housing (Box 12)
    - Department of Housing, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Department of Human Resources, 1979 (Box 12)
    - IV-D Capius Mittimus Pilot Study, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
    - DHR Management Review of the Personnel Div., 1985-1986 (Box 12)
    - Social Security IV Child Enforcement Program (AFDC) DHE, 1980-1987 (Box 12)
    - IV D (Box 12)
    - Task Force on Child Support Enforcement, 1983 (Box 12)
    - DHR Management Review, 1983 (Box 12)
    - DHR Management Study, 1983 (Box 12)
    - DHR Board of Education and Services for the Blind, 1985 (Box 12)
    - DAS Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities, 1984-1986 (Box 12)
    - CHRO Affirmative Action Regulations, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Department of Income Maintenance (Box 12)
    - DAS Delinquent Accounts, 1984 (Box 13)
    - DAS Bureau of Information Systems and Data Processing, 1985-1987 (Box 13)
    - DAS BISDP EDP Advisory Council, 1980-1982 (Box 13)
    - DAS BISDP 1st year Long Range DP Planning, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
    - DAS BISDP Long Range DP Planning Task Force, 1981-1984 (Box 13)
    - BISDP P.C. Users Group (Box 13)
    - DAS BISDP Small Computer Policies and Standards (Box 13)
    - Report to Commissioner Negri, The State of Data Processing Procurement, 1987 (Box 13)
    - DAS Personnel, 1983-1987 (Box 13)
    - DAS Personnel Item 265Q (Box 13)
    - DAS Objective Job Evaluation, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Advisory Committee Objective Job Evaluation DAS (Box 13)
    - DAS Personnel Executive Pay Plan Update, 1987 (Box 13)
    - DAS Personnel Objective Business Management Group 2, 1986 (Box 13)
    - Management Class OBJ, 1986 (Box 13)
    - Objective Job Evaluation, 1986 (Box 13)
    - DAS Personnel Objective Job Evaluation, 1985 (Box 13)
    - DAS Personnel Regulation for Application Rejection Appeal Process, 1981 (Box 13)
    - CT State Senior Executive Service Board (Box 13)
    - State Suggestion Program Review Panel, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
    - State of CT Suggestion Program (Box 13)
    - State Employee Suggestion Program DAS, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
    - Employee Suggestion Award Program, 1984 (Box 13)
    - DAS/Personnel/Comptroller, State Travel, 1984 (Box 13)
    - DAS Worker's Comp. Pilot, 1984 (Box 13)
    - DAS Personnel Workers' Comp., 1986 (Box 13)
    - Worker's Compensation, 1977-1982 (Box 13)
    - Worker's Comp. Guidelines Awards Div. A.G., 1980-1983 (Box 13)
    - Department of Public Works, 1987 (Box 13)
    - DAS Bureau of Public Works Building Maintenance Services, 1981 (Box 13)
    - DAS B.P.W. Courthouse Maintenance, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
    - Court House Project (Box 13)
    - DAS Bureau of Purchases (Box 13)
    - DAS Bureau of Purchases - Office of Fleet Operations (Box 13)
    - Bureau of Purchases, Monthly Vehicle Usage Reports, 1986 (Box 13)
    - DAS/OPM (M&E) State Passenger Car Management, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Department on Aging (Box 13)
    - Department on Aging, ConnPace Program, 1986 (Box 13)
    - Department of Agriculture (Box 13)
    - CT Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 13)
    - Office of Attorney General
    - Department of Banking, 1984
    - Copy of Master Lease Agreement Wang (Box 14)
    - Laboratories and State of CT, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Wang Statewide Users Group, 1985 (Box 14)
    - OPM - Energy (Box 14)
    - Energy Assistance Program, 1983 (Box 14)
    - DHR Energy Assistance Program, 1983-1984 (Box 14)
    - Energy Audits, CEAP, LIWAP, 1983-1984 (Box 14)
    - Energy Facility Contract Pilot, 1982-1983 (Box 14)
    - Winter Energy Plan, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - OPM Evacuation Plan (Box 14)
    - OPM Fair Labor Standards Act, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Governor's Council on Voluntary Action, 1986 (Box 14)
    - OPM Intergovernmental Relations (Box 14)
    - OPM IGR Procedures Manual, 1987 (Box 14)
    - OPM Justice Planning CJIS, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Legislation, 1987-1988 (Box 14)
    - Legislation, 1986-1987 (Box 14)
    - OPM Justice Planning Division, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Legislative Material, 1983-1987 (Box 14)
    - OPM Library (Box 14)
    - Management Development Committee, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Affirmative Action Program, 1983-1987 (Box 15)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 15)
    - Affirmative Action Proposal (Box 15)
    - Statewide Affirmative Action Program, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
    - Affirmative Action, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
    - CT Affirmative Action Officers (Box 15)
    - Agency Management Analysts (Box 15)
    - American Management Assn. (Box 15)
    - American Compensation Assn. (Box 15)
    - Commission on Child Support (Box 15)
    - Child Support Commission, 1985-1986 (Box 15)
    - Child Support Commission, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Citizens Crime Commission (Box 15)
    - CT Conference of Municipalities (Box 15)
    - CT Resources Recovery Authority (Box 15)
    - Eastern Regional Conference of The Council of State Governments (Box 15)
    - Council of State Governments (Box 15)
    - Committees, Commissions, Councils and Assignments (Box 15)
    - C.H.E.F.A., 1982-1987 (Box 15)
    - C.H.E.F.A., 1981-1983 (Box 15)
    - C.H.E.F.A., 1977-1980 (Box 16)
    - Comptroller - Retirement, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Delaware, State of (Box 16)
    - Digest of Administrative Reports (Box 16)
    - Christopher Dodd - U.S. Senate (Box 16)
    - General (Box 16)
    - Hazardous Waste Management (Box 16)
    - Idaho, State of (Box 16)
    - Internships (Box 16)
    - Office of Management and Budget (Box 16)
    - Management Advisory Council (Box 16)
    - MIP, 1986-1987 (Box 16)
    - MIP 1984-1985 (Box 16)
    - MIP 1983-1984 (Box 16)
    - MIP, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
    - MIP, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
    - MIP PIP, 1985-1986 (Box 16)
    - OPM 1982-1983 MIP Objectives (Box 16)
    - MIP 1984 OPM Objectives (Box 16)
    - M&E MIP Objectives, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
    - Management Incentives Program (MIP), 1980-1981 (Box 16)
    - MIP OPM and Division Mission Statements (Box 16)
    - Management Incentive Program (MIP), 1978-1979 (Box 16)
    - MIP Forms (Box 16)
    - MIP (Box 16)
    - MIP (Box 16)
    - Extra-OPM Management System Manual (Box 16)
    - Management Task Force Reports (Box 16)
    - June 30 Management Task Force Reports (Box 16)
    - OPM Management Task Force Master Contracts, 1981 (Box 16)
    - Maslig (Box 16)
    - Maslig 14th Annual Workshop for Government Analysts and Managers, 1986 (Box 16)
    - Maslig Conference, 1982 (Box 16)
    - 7th Annual Workshop Maslig, 1979 (Box 16)
    - Assn. of Management Analysts in State and Local Government (Maslig) Workshop and Conference, 1978 (Box 16)
    - Maslig 16th Annual Conference, 1979 (Box 16)
    - National Association of State Budget Officers (Box 17)
    - Nasbo Conference, 1986 (Box 17)
    - NFBPA CT Chapter, 1987 (Box 17)
    - National Governors' Association (Box 17)
    - NFBPA Forum, 1986 (Box 17)
    - National Forum for Black Public Administrators (Box 17)
    - New Jersey, State of (Box 17)
    - City of New York (Box 17)
    - New York State (Box 17)
    - North Carolina (Box 17)
    - Oregon, State of (Box 17)
    - Outpatient Clinic Feasibility Study, Niantic (Box 17)
    - Veterans Home and Hospital (Box 17)
    - Overtime, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Overtime Study - Depts. of Mental Health and Retardation (Box 17)
    - Overtime Study (Box 17)
    - Pennsylvania, State of (Box 17)
    - Pa. Cost Reduction Report, 1983-1984 (Box 17)
    - Performance-based Incentive System (Box 17)
    - Prison and Jail Overcrowding Commission, 1987 (Box 17)
    - Prison and Jail Overcrowding Commission Subcommittee on Probation, 1986 (Box 17)
    - Prison and Jail Overcrowding, 1984-1986 (Box 17)
    - Site Selection (Box 17)
    - OPM Commission on Jail and Prison Overcrowding (Box 17)
    - Proposed Recommendations - Prison and Jail Overcrowding Commission, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Task Force on Jail and Prison Overcrowding (Box 17)
    - Jail and Prison Task Force (Box 18)
    - Reorganization (Box 18)
    - State Science, Engineering and technology Program (SSET) (Box 18)
    - Subscription, Publications, et. (Box 18)
    - Telecommunications Task Force, 1984 (Box 18)
    - United Way, 1982 (Box 18)
    - Virginia, State of (Box 18)
    - Washington, State of (Box 18)
    - State of Washington - Sunset review of Positions (Box 18)
    - W.K. Williams & Co. Management Classification Study (Box 18)
    - Workfare (Box 18)
    - Wyoming, State of (Box 18)
    - R & D Positions, 1980 (Box 18)
    - Health Care Contingency, 1981 (Box 18)
    - Emergency Contingency Plan, 1983 (Box 18)
- Series 15. Energy Division, 1960-1990; 31.25 cubic feet
  - Coastal Energy Impact Program, 1977-1986; 1990-007
    - Coastal Energy Impact Program An Evaluation, 1980 August (Box 1)
    - Uniroyal, Inc. Middlebury Conn. (Box 1)
    - CEIP meeting - LSB (Box 1)
    - CEIP 308(b) (Box 1)
    - CEIP (Box 1)
    - #8 Stratford CEIP Proposal, 1981 (Box 1)
    - #8 Stratford SWRPA Proposal, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Westport CEIP Proposal/Contracts, 1980 (Box 1)
    - #9 Westport CEIP Proposal, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Fay Spofford and Thorndike Study (Box 1)
    - CEIP Application, 1978 (Box 1)
    - A-95, 1981 (Box 1)
    - CAM Correspondence (Box 1)
    - CEIP Accomplishments (Box 1)
    - CEIP Directly Affecting (Box 1)
    - CEIP State Project (Box 1)
    - Coastal Energy Impact Program (Box 1)
    - CEIP Planning 308(c) (Box 1)
    - CEIP Boundaries (Box 1)
    - CEIP Communications (Box 1)
    - Unfiled material (Box 2)
    - NA-82-AA-D-CZ52 (Box 2)
    - NA-83-AA-D-CZ010 (Box 2)
    - Amendment 4 (Box 2)
    - CEIP Grant Award #04-8-M01-327 (Box 2)
    - Application, 1981 (Box 2)
    - CEIP Grant Award #NA-80-AA-D-CZ042 Amendment No. 3 (Box 2)
    - Unfiled material (Box 2)
    - CEIP Grant Award #NA-80-AA-D-CZ042 Amendment No. 1 (Box 2)
    - Connors Sales Company, Inc. (Box 2)
    - CEIP Grant Award #NA-81-AA-D-CZ130 New Haven (Box 2)
    - New Haven Report (CEIP) (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 2)
    - CEIP Press Releases (Box 2)
    - CEIP 1980-1982 Grant (Box 2)
    - CMEC Proposal (Box 2)
    - Coastal States Organization (Box 2)
    - Credit Assistance 308 (d) (Box 2)
    - Department of Agriculture / Supplemental Material (Box 2)
    - EIS Guidelines (Box 2)
    - 1981 G-2 Process (Box 2)
    - Lobbying (Box 2)
    - CEIP New Forms (Box 2)
    - CEIP Engineering (Box 2)
    - CEIP Workshop, 1981 (Box 2)
    - NEPA (Box 2)
    - New Orleans Meeting, 1980 (Box 2)
    - OCS Administration Grant 308(c) (2) (Box 2)
    - Traverse City, Michigan CEIP Meeting, 1980 August (Box 2)
    - Trip Information (Box 2)
    - 1982-1986 Budget Estimates (Box 2)
    - (Status) Federal Regs, Budgets, Critical Dates, etc. (Box 2)
    - 4. MSI - Thames River plants (Box 2)
    - #4 East Lyme CEIP proposal, 1981 (Box 3)
    - DEP Contract - Duplicates - Oil Spill (Box 3)
    - Norwalk 1980 CEIP Proposal/Contract (Box 3)
    - #13 New Haven CEIP proposal, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Son of Rip Rap (Box 3)
    - New Haven Tank Farm Study (Box 3)
    - #1 DEP CEIP proposal, 1981 (Box 3)
    - #5 DEP Marine Fisheries CEIP proposals, 1981 (Box 3)
    - FY 79 CEIP - DEP and Norwalk 308 (b) (Box 3)
    - #6 DEP/CAM CEIP proposal, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Salt Marsh (Box 3)
    - 2b. New Haven purchase salt marsh(es) (Box 3)
    - Aqua culture, Dept. of/1980 CEIP project contractor (Box 3)
    - #2 Energy Division CEIP Proposal, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Scientific Advisor (Box 3)
    - Mores on CEIP Projects, 1980 June-July (Box 3)
    - New Haven Rip Rap file II (Box 4)
    - 7. RPA-SCC New Haven Trans Impacts (Box 4)
    - DEP Oil Spill Cooperative 1980 CEIP project/contract (Box 4)
    - 1. DEP/Hazardous Wastes - Oil Spill Training (Box 4)
    - OPM Project with Energy Division (Box 4)
    - #14 GBRPA CEIP proposal, 1981 (Box 4)
    - 2e. New Haven coal policy (Box 4)
    - Index to files (Box 4)
    - Wind Articles (Box 4)
    - Tank Farms (Box 4)
    - Population #'s/Census info (Box 4)
    - Oil Spill Articles (Box 4)
    - Natural Gas Articles (Box 4)
    - Long Island Sound (Box 4)
    - George's Bank Articles (Box 4)
    - CEIP Grant Award #NA-80-AA-D-CZ042 Original Award (Box 4)
    - 10. GBRPA - Solid Wastes (Box 4)
    - 5. DEP/NRC - Marine Data Clearinghouse (Box 4)
    - 2d. New Haven - Boat Ramp Study (Box 4)
    - 2c. New Haven UI - Aquaculture (Box 4)
    - 9. DPUC Coastal Energy Fixtures (Box 4)
    - 8. CRERPA Gateway/Oil Spill (Box 4)
    - 6. SCSSC - Oil Spill Effects/Clams, Oysters (Box 4)
    - 3. MSI (UConn) Waves (Box 4)
    - 2a. New Haven computer model (Box 4)
    - Southeast RPA (Box 4)
    - 11. DEP/Water Compl. Lease notes (Box 4)
    - CAM-CEIP project contract, 1980 (Box 4)
    - 2. New Haven cover letter (Box 4)
    - #12 VRPA CEIP proposal, 1981 (Box 4)
    - #3 SERPA CEIP proposal, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Unfiled material (Box 5)
    - Acid rain articles (Box 5)
    - CEIP articles (Box 5)
    - CEIP other states proposals (Box 5)
    - CEIP Other States (Box 5)
    - CEIP Port Consultant List (Box 5)
    - General Energy Articles (Box 5)
    - General Environment Articles (Box 5)
    - CEIP Impact Strategy, 1980 (Box 5)
    - Audits/evaluations (Box 5)
    - Allotments CEIP (Box 5)
    - Intra State Allocation Process, 1982 (Box 5)
    - CAM Review, 1981 (Box 5)
    - CEIP Letter of Credit (Box 5)
    - CEIP Lead Agency Designation Grasso Letter (Box 5)
    - Management Audit (Box 5)
    - OCS Revenue Sharing HR Bill 4597 (Box 5)
    - CEIP Grant Administration (Box 5)
    - Memos to Grantees (Box 5)
    - Transition Memos - CEIP (Box 5)
    - Federal Regulations CEIP (Box 5)
    - 308 (c) (3) (Box 5)
    - 306-308 consolidation (Box 5)
    - CEIP General Information (Box 5)
    - CEIP Workshop, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Extension Request/Grant Changes (Box 5)
    - CEIP Application, 1982 (Box 5)
    - CEIP Projects (Box 5)
    - New Contract Package (Box 5)
    - Applicant Finalists, Rewrites, New Data, etc. (Box 5)
    - CEIP Proposals, 1982 (Box 5)
    - 1982 CEIP Allotment (and final regs) (Box 5)
    - CEIP Records/Audit (Box 5)
    - Application checklist, regulations, etc. (Box 5)
    - CEIP Performance Reports (Box 5)
    - Federal Letters (Box 5)
    - Letters to Feds (Box 5)
    - Backup material to requisition #2 for Oceanic Society, 1981 July 7 (Box 5)
    - Backup material for requisition #4 Oceanic Society, 1981 September 10 (Box 5)
  - Atomic Energy Coordinator
    - 1966-1969, 1979-1983, 1992-014
      - Atomic Energy Development Activities, 1966-1969 (Box 1)
      - Unfiled material, 1979-1983 (Box 1)
    - 1960-1977, 2002-068
      - Atomic Energy (Box 1)
      - Atomic Energy Commission, U.S. (Box 1)
      - Atomic Energy Commission U.S. Papers (Box 1)
      - Atomic Industrial Forum Publications (Box 1)
      - AE Colleges, State Technical (Box 1)
      - AE Coordinator Functions, Conn. (Box 1)
      - AE Coordinator, Other States (Box 1)
      - AE Definitions (Box 1)
      - AE Education, Courses, Conferences and Seminars (Box 1)
      - AE Grants, Loans (Box 1)
      - AE Licenses, etc. (Box 1)
      - New England River Basin Commission (Box 1)
      - Northeast Utilities (Box 1)
      - Legislation, Regulations, Rulings, Opinions Conn. (Box 1)
      - Legislation, Regulations, Rulings, Opinions Federal (Box 1)
      - Legislation, Regulations, Rulings, Opinions Other Federal (Box 1)
      - Legislation, Regulations, Rulings, Opinions States Other than Conn. (Box 1)
      - State Water Resources Commission Hearing (Box 1)
      - Records Stored at Rocky Hill (Box 1)
      - Draft Environmental Statement. Conn. Yankee NPP, 1973 March (Box 1)
      - Nuclear Power Plants, Connecticut Yankee, Haddam (Box 1)
      - Nuclear Power Plants Conn., Millstone 1, Waterford (Box 2)
      - Nuclear Power Plants Conn., Millstone 2, Waterford (Box 2)
      - Nuclear Power Plants Conn., Millstone 3 (Box 2)
      - Nuclear Power Plants Other States and Conn. (Box 2)
      - Conn. Center for Research, Training and Education (CONCRETE) (Box 2)
      - Conn. Research Center (Box 2)
      - Conn. Research Commission (Box 2)
      - University Research Institute of Conn. (URIC) (Box 2)
      - AE Uses (Box 2)
      - Atomic Energy Correspondence, etc. (Box 2)
  - Files, 1972-1990; 1996-012
    Unprocessed.
    - Energy Planning, 1973-1980
      - Data Processing (Box 1)
      - DECONTROL (Box 1)
      - Deep Water Ports (Box 1)
      - Department of Energy (Box 1)
      - Deregulation (Box 1)
      - Divestiture (Box 1)
      - Economic Data - Conn. (Box 1)
      - Economic Planning (Box 1)